SUBTITLE & SYNC AND CORRECTED :
JAVANI65@GMAIL.COM
Oh,Excuse me.
I don't think that was you.
Oh,My all familiar.
See,He's still hug his parent's.
Ellie.
Manny.
Hold me.
When the world fall apart.
No matter how long it take.
I WILL FIND YOU.
This three greatest hero,
Manny?
You're alive.
Hey,Sid this is my first bath in decade's.
I don't wanna see that.
Will keep it together.
My mamma told me once that bad new's was just good new's in disguise.
Was this before she abandoned you?
Yes it was.
I'll push him over ball.
You guy's say's it was an accident.
I'm in.
This summer.
Battle station.
Surrender your ship,
Or face my fury.
Two word's:Anger Managment.
The end of the world.
We all gonna survive this.
Okay maybe They won't.
He's just a tip of the Iceberg.
Hey,new fellas,How about you and us get
against the pirate's.
You have got no idea what im saying,Do you?
May I try?
That the guy.
Every one please Don't panic.
Fire.
No one gonna stop me from getting back to my family.
Come on Ocean,This is the best you can do?
Holy Crap.
ICE AGE : CONTINENTAL DRIFT
You're pretty soft and sober.
Excuse me,I happened to be the merciless assassin.
Diego,Hey I made another cool necklace.
He keep's loosing them.
SUBTITLE & SYNC AND CORRECTED :
JAVANI65@GMAIL.COM
www.moviesubtitles.org